Guide to the School of Nursing, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1921-1979; Accession 19ND-A-410
  - Series I
    - Operating Room Course, 1946-47
      - Young, Electra Rumsey OR Course, 1946-47 (Box 148, Folder 1745)
      - Young, Joan V. OR Course, 1946-47 (Box 148, Folder 1746)
    - Operating Room Course, 1946-47
      - Duin,Josefina OR Course, 1946 (Box 149, Folder 1747)
      - Hicok, Harriet OR Course, 1946 (Box 149, Folder 1748)
      - Janell, Virginia OR Course, 1946 (Box 149, Folder 1749)
      - Lukowski, Marion C. OR Course, 1946 (Box 149, Folder 1750)
      - McClury, Mary OR Course, 1946 (Box 149, Folder 1751)
      - Sturgeon, Martha B. OR Course, 1946 (Box 149, Folder 1752)
    - Operating Room Course, 1945-46
      - Brunson, Blanche OR Course, 1945-46 (Box 149, Folder 1753)
      - Brownell, Mrs. Elaine G. OR Course, 1945-46 (Box 149, Folder 1754)
      - Davia, Lena OR Course, 1945-46 (Box 149, Folder 1755)
      - DeLima, Alvera OR Course, 1945-46 (Box 149, Folder 1756)
      - Kuenzi, Pu1ine J. OR Course, 1945-46 (Box 149, Folder 1757)
      - Lassiter, G. Louise OR Course, 1945-46 (Box 149, Folder 1758)
      - Moore Francer S. OR Course, 1945-46 (Box 149, Folder 1759)
      - Senst, Mary OR Course, 1945-46 (Box 149, Folder 1760)
    - Operating Room Course, 1945
      - Clay, Florence M. OR Course, 1945 (Box 149, Folder 1761)
      - Mason, Margaret OR Course, 1945 (Box 149, Folder 1762)
      - Schwan, Mora C. OR Course, 1945 (Box 149, Folder 1763)
    - Operating Room Course, 1944-45
      - Ashby, Florence E. OR Course, 1944-45 (Box 150, Folder 1764)
      - Cunning, Dorothy L. OR Course, 1944-45 (Box 150, Folder 1765)
      - Kereks, Loyola C. OR Course, 1944-45 (Box 150, Folder 1766)
      - Pomeroy, Florence E. OR Course, 1944-45 (Box 150, Folder 1767)
      - Ziegler, Phyllis A. OR Course, 1944-45 (Box 150, Folder 1768)
    - Operating Room Course, 1944
      - Cashman, Margaret A. OR Course, 1944 (Box 150, Folder 1769)
      - Buckley, Mrs. Elizabeth K. OR Course, 1944 (Box 150, Folder 1770)
      - Cox, Vera Eileen OR Course, 1944 (Box 150, Folder 1771)
      - Weaselhoeft, Henrietta OR Course, 1944 (Box 150, Folder 1772)
      - Kixmi1ler, Charlotte M.OR Course, 1944 (Box 150, Folder 1773)
    - Operating Room Course, 1943-44
      - Enos, Lucy De Reid OR Course, 1943-44 (Box 150, Folder 1774)
      - Hansen, Ellen OR Course, 1943-44 (Box 150, Folder 1775)
      - Mulseed, Annette OR Course, 1943-44 (Box 150, Folder 1776)
      - Simmons, Mary Lois OR Course, 1943-44 (Box 150, Folder 1777)
      - Pritz, Rose OR Course, 1943-44 (Box 150, Folder 1778)
    - Operating Room Course, 1943
      - Akey, Virginia OR Course, 1943 (Box 150, Folder 1779)
      - Herrity, Kathleen OR Course, 1943 (Box 150, Folder 1780)
      - Sito, Sophia J. OR Course, 1943 (Box 150, Folder 1781)
      - Weise, Ruth D. OR Course, 1943 (Box 150, Folder 1782)
      - Wilson, Delvee OR Course, 1943 (Box 150, Folder 1783)
    - Operating Room Course, 1942-43
      - Beckwith, Lucille OR Course, 1942-43 (Box 150, Folder 1784)
      - Bevan, Beatrice OR Course, 1942-43 (Box 151, Folder 1785)
      - Doris, Dunkwine OR Course, 1942-43 (Box 151, Folder 1786)
      - Harmon, Laura E. OR Course, 1942-43 (Box 151, Folder 1787)
      - Rashenor, Dorothea OR Course, 1942-43 (Box 151, Folder 1788)
    - Operating Room Course, 1942
      - Beers, Mary H. OR Course, 1942 (Box 151, Folder 1789)
      - Casey, Josephine J. OR Course, 1942 (Box 151, Folder 1790)
      - Fryer, Esther L. OR Course, 1942 (Box 151, Folder 1791)
      - Higgins, Elizabeth OR Course, 1942 (Box 151, Folder 1792)
      - Phillips, Meta OR Course, 1942 (Box 151, Folder 1793)
    - Operating Room Course, 1941-42
      - Doherty, Mary V.R Course, 1941-42 (Box 151, Folder 1794)
      - Hopkins, Priscilla M. OR Course, 1941-42 (Box 151, Folder 1795)
      - Judge, Jane C. OR Course, 1941-42 (Box 151, Folder 1796)
      - Nagle, Lorraine OR Course, 1941-42 (Box 151, Folder 1797)
      - Squatrito, Joy F. OR Course, 1941-42 (Box 151, Folder 1798)
    - Bibliography, 1941-1942 (Box 151, Folder 1799)
    - Lecture and Class Notes (Box 151, Folder 1800)
    - Refresher Course, Correspondence, Misc. (Box 151, Folder 1801)
    - Refresher Course, Reports of (Box 151, Folder 1802)
    - Refresher Course, Rolls, Grades, Examinations (Box 151, Folder 1803)
    - Refresher Course, Outlines, Bibliography (Box 151, Folder 1804)
    - Copies of Letters to Club Presidents (Box 151, Folder 1805)
    - Refresher Course Certificates (Box 151, Folder 1806)
    - Auditor Refresher Course, 1942-43 (Box 152, Folder 1807)
    - Auditor Operating Room Course, 1942-46 (Box 152, Folder 1808)
    - Federal Aid Refrepher Course, 1942-43 (Box 152, Folder 1809)
    - Form Letters for Course II (Box 152, Folder 1810)
    - Application Blanks Course I (Box 152, Folder 1811)
    - Federal Aid Refresher Course, 1941-42 Current and Original Data (Box 152, Folder 1812)
    - Federal Aid, Proposed Summer Course (Box 152, Folder 1813)
    - Available Housing, Sterling (Box 152, Folder 1814)
    - Operating Room Course, 1945-46, Fed. Grant (Box 152, Folder 1815)
    - Operating Room Course, 1944-45, Fed. Grant (Box 152, Folder 1816)
    - Operating Room Course, 1943-44, Application, Budget Supporting Data (Box 152, Folder 1817)
    - Operating Room Course, 1942-45 (Box 152, Folder 1818)
    - Operating Room Course, 1941-42, Original and Current Data (Box 152, Folder 1819)
    - Federal Aid Uncompleted Blanks for Reimbursement (missing) (Box 152, Folder 1820)
    - Federal Aid Misc. Correspondence (Box 152, Folder 1821)
    - Federal Aid Course Correspondence Publ. Health Nursing (Box 152, Folder 1822)
    - Cadet Nurse Corp. -Mlmeographed Material (Box 152, Folder 1823)
    - USPHS Post-Grad. Courses (other than OR) Correspondence and Mdmeo. Material (Box 152, Folder 1824)
    - Case Study Committee (Box 153, Folder 1825)
    - Record Committee Policies (Box 153, Folder 1826)
    - Student records
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted until Januay 1, 2025
      - 1926 (Box 153, Folder 1827-1828)
      - 1927 (Box 153, Folder 1829)
      - 1928 (Box 153, Folder 1830)
      - 1929 (Box 153, Folder 1831)
      - 1930 (Box 153, Folder 1832)
      - 1931 (Box 153, Folder 1833)
      - 1932 (Box 154, Folder 1834)
      - 1933 (Box 154, Folder 1835)
      - 1934 (Box 154, Folder 1836)
      - 1935 (Box 154, Folder 1837)
      - 1936 (Box 154, Folder 1838)
      - 1937 (Box 154, Folder 1839)
      - 1938 (Box 154, Folder 1840)
      - 1939 (Box 154, Folder 1841)
      - 1940 (Box 154, Folder 1842)
      - 1941 (Box 154, Folder 1843)
      - 1942 (Box 154, Folder 1844)
      - 1943 (Box 155, Folder 1845)
      - 1944 (Box 155, Folder 1846)
      - 1945 (Box 155, Folder 1847)
      - 1946 (Box 155, Folder 1848)
      - 1947 (Box 155, Folder 1849)
      - 1948 (Box 155, Folder 1850)
      - 1949 (Box 155, Folder 1851)
      - 1950 (Box 155, Folder 1852)
    - YSN A Compilation of Students' Records in Pediatric Nursing, 1929 (Box 155, Folder 1853)
    - Early Schedules and Plans of Courses (Box 155, Folder 1854)
    - Course Outlines (Box 155, Folder 1855)
      - Textbooks (Box 155, Folder 1856)
      - Schedules (Box 155, Folder 1857)
      - Reading Lists (Box 155, Folder 1858)
      - Lettering (Box 155, Folder 1859)
      - Anatomy (Box 156, Folder 1860)
      - Bacteriology (Box 156, Folder 1861)
      - History of Nursing (Box 156, Folder 1862)
      - Social Aspects (Box 156, Folder 1863)
      - Pathology (Box 156, Folder 1864)
      - ClinicalPsychology (Box 156, Folder 1865)
      - Professional Adjustments (Box 156, Folder 1866)
      - Nutrition (Box 156, Folder 1867)
      - Occupational Health (Box 156, Folder 1868)
      - Pediatric Nursing (Box 156, Folder 1869)
      - Physiology (Box 156, Folder 1870)
      - Physical Therapy (Box 156, Folder 1871)
      - Out-Patient Department (Box 157, Folder 1872)
      - Psychosomatic Nursing (Box 157, Folder 1873)
      - Public Health Nursing (Box 157, Folder 1874)
      - Therapeutics (Box 157, Folder 1875)
      - Medical Nursing (Box 157, Folder 1876)
      - Communicable Disease (Box 157, Folder 1877)
      - Surgical Nursing (Box 157, Folder 1878)
      - Time Study -Margaret Tracy Care of Surgical Patients Determining Costs of Nursing Education (Box 157, Folder 1879)
      - Medical Surgical Nursing (Box 157, Folder 1880)
      - Operating Room Nursing (Box 157, Folder 1881)
      - Nursing School (Box 157, Folder 1882)
      - Pediatrics (Box 157, Folder 1883)
      - Obs. -Gyn. (Box 158, Folder 1884)
      - Psychiatry (Box 158, Folder 1885)
      - Red Cross Course (Box 158, Folder 1886)
      - Ward Administration (Box 158, Folder 1887)
      - Senior Seminars (Box 158, Folder 1888)
      - Communicable Disease Affiliations (Box 158, Folder 1889)
      - Medicine Affil. (Box 158, Folder 1890)
      - Pediatric (Box 158, Folder 1891)
      - Examination Questions (Box 158, Folder 1892)
      - Advanced Psychiatric Nursing (Box 158, Folder 1893)
      - Objectives General Education (Box 158, Folder 1894)
      - Staff Education (Box 158, Folder 1895)
      - Estimate of Student Progress (Box 158, Folder 1896)
      - Time Study (Box 158, Folder 1897)
      - Correlation of theory - prac. Records (Box 158, Folder 1898)
      - Study-Nursing Procedures (Box 158, Folder 1899)
      - Analysis of YSN Courses (Box 158, Folder 1900)
      - Student Health (Box 158, Folder 1901)
      - General (Box 158, Folder 1902)
      - Evaluation - Grading (Box 158, Folder 1903)
      - YSN Graduates (Box 158, Folder 1904)
      - Program - Visitors (Box 158, Folder 1905)
      - 1942 YSN Survey Report (Box 158, Folder 1906)
    - YSN Hospital Ward Routines, 1932 (Box 159, Folder 1907)
    - YSN Nursing Procedures, 1932-33 (Box 159, Folder 1908)
    - Complete Set - School and Hospital Records (Box 159, Folder 1909-1910)
    - Communicable Disease-Waterbury Students (Box 159, Folder 1911)
    - Experience Records (Box 160, Folder 1912)
    - Yale University Clippings (Box 160, Folder 1913)
    - YSN Case Studies (Box 160, Folder 1914)
    - Report First Grading of Nursing Schools, 1942 (Box 160, Folder 1915)
    - Report Second Grading of Nursing Schools, 1945 (Box 160, Folder 1916)
    - Study Evening - Night Duty, 1950 (Box 160, Folder 1917)
    - Ward Administration Reports, 1945 (Box 160, Folder 1918)
    - Nursing Education (Box 161, Folder 1919)
    - Student Education Preparatbn and Philosophy (Box 161, Folder 1920)
    - Summary Records (Box 161, Folder 1921)
    - Education Research and Testing Programs (Box 161, Folder 1922-1923)
    - The Registered Trained Practical Nurse (Box 161, Folder 1924)
    - Health Reports, YSN (Box 162, Folder 1925)
    - Nursing Education Collegiate (Box 162, Folder 1926-1927)
    - The New Haven Hospital (Box 162, Folder 1928)
    - Trends in Nursing Education, 1947 (Box 162, Folder 1929)
    - Emotional Factors Childbearing Woman, 1947 (Box 162, Folder 1930)
    - The State Rheumatic Fever Program, by G.M.Roshon, 1947 (Box 163, Folder 1931)
    - Adjustment of Children with Cerebral Palsy, 1948 (Box 163, Folder 1932)
    - Role of the Practical Nurse, 1948 (Box 163, Folder 1933)
    - Role of the Practical Nurse, 1948, Dean's Office (Box 163, Folder 1934)
    - Personnel Policies in Nursing, 1948 (Box 163, Folder 1935)
    - Army and Navy General Hospital, 1947 (Box 163, Folder 1936)
    - Gorgas Hospital, on, Canal Zone, Named in, 1928 (photographs) (Box 163, Folder 1937)
    - Brooke General Hospital Fort Sam Houston Texas (photographs) (Box 163, Folder 1938)
    - Rooming -In, What Is It?, 1948 (Box 164, Folder 1939)
    - Development of Psychiatric Nursing, 1948 (Box 164, Folder 1940)
    - Radio Script -The Professional Nursell, 1948 (Box 164, Folder 1941)
    - Community Aspect -Mat. Child Care, 1948 (Box 164, Folder 1942)
    - Geriatrics -Orthopedic Needs, 1948 (Box 164, Folder 1943)
    - Nursing Care of Patients with Alcoholism, 1948 (Box 164, Folder 1944)
    - Elective Experience Affiliations, 1950 (Box 164, Folder 1945)
    - Study -Aims of Collegiate School, 1950 (Box 164, Folder 1946)
    - General Medical Library (photographs) (Box 164, Folder 1947)
    - TripIer General Hospital Honolulu, T.H. (photographs) (Box 164, Folder 1948)
    - eport of Elective Experience, 1951, vo1.I (Box 165, Folder 1949)
    - Report of Elective Experience, 1951, vol. II (Box 165, Folder 1950)
    - Report of Elective Experience, 1951, vol. III (Box 165, Folder 1951)
    - Report of Elective Experience, 1952 (Box 165, Folder 1952)
    - Senior Elective Experiences, 1953 (Box 165, Folder 1953-1954)
    - Study -Evaluation Reports, 1950 (Box 165, Folder 1955)
    - Elective Clinical Experiences YSN, 1950 (Box 165, Folder 1956)
    - Study -Rheumatic Fever, 1950 (Box 165, Folder 1956)
    - A Compilation of Student Records Required for Course in Medical Nursing, 1931
      - Bulletin 113 (Box 166, Folder 1958-59)
      - Curriculum Misc. Material (Box 166, Folder 1960)
      - Anatomy (Box 166, Folder 1961)
      - Bacteriology, 1924-33 (Box 166, Folder 1962)
      - Chemistry YSN, 1924-34 (Box 166, Folder 1963)
      - Communicable Disease (Box 166, Folder 1964)
      - Dermatology (Box 166, Folder 1965)
      - Dispensary (Box 166, Folder 1966)
      - Ethics (Box 166, Folder 1967)
      - History of Nursing (Box 166, Folder 1968)
      - Human Behavior, 1932-33 (Box 166, Folder 1969)
      - Medical Class and Lectures YSN, 1926-35 (Box 167, Folder 1970)
      - Nursery School (Box 167, Folder 1971)
      - Nutrition Diet, Diet Therapy Monthly Reports (Box 167, Folder 1972)
      - Pediatric Misc. Material (Box 167, Folder 1973)
      - Nutrition -Diet Therapy, 1924-35 (Box 167, Folder 1974)
      - Obs. Gyn. Outlines Exams, 1926-29 (Box 167, Folder 1975)
      - Pathology, 1925-26 (Box 167, Folder 1976)
      - Pediatrics YSN Outlines, 1927-40 (Box 168, Folder 1977-1978)
      - Physiology, 1924-34 (Box 168, Folder 1979)
      - Physical Education (Box 168, Folder 1980)
      - A Compilation of Student Records Required for Course in Medical Nursing, 1931 (cont'd)
        - Principles and Practice of Nursing, Exams, Outlines, 1924-35 (Box 168, Folder 1981)
        - Principles and Practice of Nursing Procedures (Box 168, Folder 1982)
        - Public Health Problems of Health and Disease (Box 168, Folder 1983)
        - Public Health Dr. Winslow's Miss Fox's Courses (Box 169, Folder 1984)
        - Psychiatry Butler Hospital, 1926 (Box 169, Folder 1985)
        - Psychology, 1926 (Box 169, Folder 1986)
        - Social Hygiene McCorkle, 1936 (Box 169, Folder 1987)
        - Surgery YSN General Including EENT -Neurology (Box 169, Folder 1988)
        - Orthopedics (Surgery) YSN (Box 169, Folder 1989)
        - Therapeutics, 1921-34 (Box 169, Folder 1990)
        - Affiliation Courses for, Misc. Material, Medical Lectures and ,Exams (Box 169, Folder 1991)
        - Pediatrics Affiliates (Box 170, Folder 1992-1993)
        - Surgery Affiliates (Box 170, Folder 1994)
        - Affiliation Communicable Diseases (Box 170, Folder 1995)
        - Graduate Courses NI51 -1929-30 (Box 170, Folder 1996)
        - Graduate Courses N154, 1930 (Box 170, Folder 1997)
        - Graduate Courses N155, -1932 (Box 170, Folder 1998)
        - Graduate Courses N155, -1933 (Box 170, Folder 1999)
        - Graduate Courses N15I, -1935 (Box 170, Folder 2000)
        - Graduate Courses N15l, -1934 (Box 170, Folder 2001)
        - Graduate Courses N25l, -1936 (Box 171, Folder 2002)
        - Graduate Courses N25l, -1937 (Box 171, Folder 2003)
    - YSN Historical Material Statistics Historical Data (Box 171, Folder 2004)
    - Miscellaneous Material Relating to School (Box 171, Folder 2006-2007)
    - John Schoolcraft Correspondence, 1938 (Box 171, Folder 2008)
    - Dept. of Personnell Study, 1938 (Box 171, Folder 2009)
    - Bureau of Appointments, 1937-42 (Box 171, Folder 2010)
    - Early Publicity booklets IHR (Box 171, Folder 2011)
    - Estimate of Hypothetical Nursing Service, 1935 (Box 172, Folder 2012)
    - Budget, YSN: New Haven Hospital, 1935 (Box 172, Folder 2013)
    - Memorandum Mr. Farn, 1937 Relating to Nursing Service (Box 172, Folder 2014)
    - Excerpts from Annual Report of Deans, 1924-58 (Box 172, Folder 2015)
    - Yale School of Nurses, 1958 (Box 172, Folder 2016)
    - Conn. State Nurses Assoc. Board of Directors
      - 1946-47 (Box 172, Folder 2017)
      - 1944-46 (Box 172, Folder 2018)
      - 1949-50 (Box 172, Folder 2019)
      - 1948-49 (Box 172, Folder 2020)
    - Conn. State Board of Examinations -Registration of Nurses, 1928-39 (Box 173, Folder 2021)
    - Graduate Nurses Assoc. of Conn., 1926-34 (Box 173, Folder 2022)
    - Annual Reports, 1956-58 (Box 173, Folder 2023)
    - Book Publishers Misc. (Box 173, Folder 2025)
    - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1944-53 (Box 173, Folder 2026)
    - Macmillan, 1935-47 (Box 173, Folder 2027)
    - W.B. Saunders, 1931-45 (Box 173, Folder 2028)
    - Bradley Hospital, 1932-59 (Box 173, Folder 2030)
    - Bursar Graduate Program, 1956-57 (Box 173, Folder 2031)
    - Bursar re Students Mental Health and Public Health Courses, 1950-56 (Box 174, Folder 2032)
    - Cardiovascular Nursing, 1959 (Box 174, Folder 2033)
    - Chemistry Correspondence, 1925-54 (Box 174, Folder 2034)
    - China Medical Board (Box 174, Folder 2035)
    - Communicable Diseases Misc., 1929-48 (Box 174, Folder 2036)
    - CLN, 1958-59 (Box 174, Folder 2037)
    - Conn. State League of Nursing Education, 1927-52 (Box 174, Folder 2038)
    - Conn. State Board of Exam for Nursing -Standard Score Means, 1954-58 ..... (Box 174, Folder 2039)
    - Board of Exams for Nursing -Advisory Committee (Box 174, Folder 2040)
    - Conn. State Board of Nursing Examiners
      - 1958-59 (Box 174, Folder 2041)
      - 1949-57 (Box 174, Folder 2042)
      - 1943 (Box 174, Folder 2043)
      - 1944-48 (Box 174, Folder 2044)
    - Publicity (Box 175, Folder 2045)
    - Dean Winternitz, 1932 (Box 175, Folder 2046)
    - Paper Adjustments, 1947 (Box 175, Folder 2047)
    - Miss Bixler,1954-Addresses (Box 175, Folder 2048)
    - Miss Bixler, 1947-53 Addresses (Box 175, Folder 2049)
    - Miss Bixler Addresses (Box 175, Folder 2050)
    - YSN Calendar (missing) (Box 175, Folder 2051)
    - Radio Address, 1947, August 10 (Box 175, Folder 2052)
    - Miss Bixler Notes for Butler Paper (Box 175, Folder 2053)
    - Miss Bixler-correspondence, 1944-48 (Box 176, Folder 2054)
    - Miss Bixler Paper for Texas (Box 176, Folder 2055)
    - Miss Bixler - Univ. News Bureau (Box 176, Folder 2056)
    - Hill Echoes, Little Rock, Arkansas, 1951 (Box 176, Folder 2057)
    - Yale Univ. New Bureau - Photos of Dean Bixler (Box 176, Folder 2058)
    - "Yale Reports" (Box 176, Folder 2059)
    - President's Committee (Box 176, Folder 2060-2061)
    - Yale Provost (Box 176, Folder 2062)
    - Dr. Stanhope Bayne-Jones (Box 176, Folder 2063)
    - Correspondence re YSN Changes, 1956 (Box 176, Folder 2064)
    - School of Nursing, 1932-38 (Box 177, Folder 2065-2067)
    - Letters re Preparation for Childbirth Program, 195657 (Box 177, Folder 2068)
    - Letters chronological order, 1957-58 (Box 177, Folder 2069-2070)
    - YSN Nurses forms, information sheets (missing) (Box 178, Folder 2071)
    - Ante-Partal Care (Box 178, Folder 2072)
    - Anesthesia - Analgesia (Box 178, Folder 2073)
    - Bibliographies (Box 178, Folder 2074)
    - Breast feeding and Lactation (Box 178, Folder 2075)
    - Complications of Labor (Box 178, Folder 2076)
    - Complications re the Newborn (Box 178, Folder 2077)
    - Complications of Pregnancies (Box 178, Folder 2078)
    - Diagnostic Measures (Box 178, Folder 2079)
    - Formula Preparation (Box 178, Folder 2080)
    - Gyn. Nursing (Box 178, Folder 2081)
    - Hemorrhage (Box 178, Folder 2082)
    - Infertility (Box 178, Folder 2083)
    - Intrapartal Care (Box 178, Folder 2084)
    - Labor (Box 178, Folder 2085)
    - Newborn Care (Box 179, Folder 2086-2088)
    - Maternal Emotions (Box 179, Folder 2089)
    - Medications (Box 179, Folder 2090)
    - Maternity Care (Box 179, Folder 2091)
    - MCA (Maternity Center Association) (Box 179, Folder 2092)
    - Multiple Pregnancy (Box 179, Folder 2093)
    - Newborn-Mature-Premature (Box 179, Folder 2094)
    - Manual for New born Infant Care (Box 179, Folder 2095)
    - Obs. Gyn. Words Frequently Used (Box 179, Folder 2096)
    - Operative Obs. (Box 179, Folder 2097)
    - Pelvimery (Box 180, Folder 2098)
    - Rooming-In (Box 180, Folder 2099)
    - Placenta-Card-Membrane (Box 180, Folder 2100)
    - Pregnancy -Physiologic Diag. (Box 180, Folder 2101)
    - Postpartum Care (Box 180, Folder 2102)
    - Prenatal Notes -Kenya -Mrs. Hiscock (Box 180, Folder 2103)
    - Premature Infants (Box 180, Folder 2104)
    - Preparation for Childbirth (Box 180, Folder 2105)
    - RH Factor (Box 180, Folder 2106)
    - Statistics (Box 181, Folder 2107)
    - Vital Statistics (Box 181, Folder 2108)
    - Unmarried Mothers (Box 181, Folder 2109)
    - Probiem of Early Infancy, 1948, Josiah Macy, Jr. (Box 181, Folder 2110)
    - Budget, 1924-29 (Box 181, Folder 2111)
    - Conn. State Board Nurse Examiners, Grading, 1950 (Box 181, Folder 2112)
    - Conn. State Department Health, 1927-59 (Box 181, Folder 2113)
    - Conn. State Legislation, 1927-59 (Box 181, Folder 2114)
    - Abruptio placenta and Placenta praevia (Box 181, Folder 2115)
    - Heart disease (Box 181, Folder 2116)
    - Nephritis (Box 181, Folder 2117)
    - Pregnancy complications (Box 181, Folder 2118)
    - Other complications (Box 181, Folder 2119)
    - Tuberculosis (Box 181, Folder 2120)
    - Venereal disease: syphilis (Box 181, Folder 2121)
  - Series II
    - Ad Hoc Committee Meetings (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - ANA Advisory Committee on Clinical Sessions for the 1962 ANA Convention -I (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - ANA Advisory Committee on Clinical Sessions for the 1962 ANA Convention -II (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - Boston Lying-In Hospital (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - Commencement 1960-61, 1961-62 (Box 182, Folder 6)
    - Committee on Admissions 1956-60 (Box 182, Folder 7)
    - Connecticut Society for Mental Hygiene -Committee on Standards and Working Conditions of State Hospital Employees (Box 182, Folder 8)
    - CSNA Standing and Special Committees (Box 182, Folder 9)
    - CSNA -President 1954-Nov 1955, 1959 (Box 182, Folder 10)
    - Curriculum Committee 1958- (Box 183, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Meetings (Dean's Folder) 1960-62 (Box 183, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Research Symposiums 1961-62 (Box 183, Folder 13)
    - Faculty Research Symposiums -1962-63 (Box 183, Folder 14)
    - Graduate Curriculum Committee -1952-58 (Box 183, Folder 15)
    - Graduate Program Committee -1956 Apr-Jun (Box 183, Folder 16)
    - Library Committee 1960 (Box 183, Folder 17)
    - Major: Maternal and Newborn Health Nursing (Box 183, Folder 18)
    - Major: Mental Health and Psychiatric Nursing (Box 183, Folder 19)
    - Major: Public Health Nursing (Box 183, Folder 20)
    - Measurements Workshop 101 -Logic and Nursing Practice Theory (Box 183, Folder 21)
    - Medical Care (Box 183, Folder 22)
    - Nursing 320&321 (Minutes) 1956-March 12 1957 (Box 184, Folder 23)
    - Nursing 320&321 (Minutes) 1957 (March-December) (Box 184, Folder 24)
    - Nursing 320&321 1958 (January-May) (Box 184, Folder 25)
    - Nursing Process (Box 184, Folder 26)
    - Psychiatric Nursing Seminar - 1961 (Box 184, Folder 27)
    - Psychiatric Nursing Seminar - 1962-63 (Fall Semester) (Box 184, Folder 28)
    - Psychiatric Nursing Seminar - 1962-63 (extra bibliography, etc.) (Box 184, Folder 29)
    - Public Health, Dept. of - 1960- (Box 184, Folder 30)